{"teammembers":[
    {
        "id": "1",
        "Question":"Question 1 of 10",
        "Q":"What does SQL stand for?",
        "Options":["Structured Query Language"," Strong Question Language"," Structured Question Language",""],
        "Answer":0
    },
    {
        "id": "2",
        "Question":"Question 2 of 10",
        "Q":"Which SQL statement is used to extract data from a database?",
        "Options":[" OPEN","GET","SELECT","EXTRACT"],
        "Answer":2
    },
    {
        "id": "3",
        "Question":"Question 3 of 10",
        "Q":"Which SQL statement is used to update data in a database?",
        "Options":["UPDATE","MODIFY","SAVE","SAVE AS"],
        "Answer":0
    },
    {
        "id": "4",
        "Question":"Question 4 of 10",
        "Q":"Which SQL statement is used to delete data from a database?",
        "Options":["REMOVE ","DELETE","COLLAPSE",""],
        "Answer":1
    },
    {
        "id": "5",
        "Question":"Question 5 of 10",
        "Q":"Which SQL statement is used to insert new data in a database?",
        "Options":["ADD NEW ","INSERT INTO","INSERT NEW",""],
        "Answer":1
    },
    {
        "id": "6",
        "Question":"Question 6 of 10",
        "Q":"With SQL, how do you select a column named 'FirstName' from a table named 'Persons'?",
        "Options":["SELECT FirstName FROM Persons","SELECT Persons.FirstName","EXTRACT FirstName FROM Persons",""],
        "Answer":0
    },
    {
        "id": "7",
        "Question":"Question 7 of 10",
        "Q":"The OR operator displays a record if ANY conditions listed are true. The AND operator displays a record if ALL of the conditions listed are true ",
        "Options":["TRUE","FALSE","",""],
        "Answer":0
    },
    {
        "id": "8",
        "Question":"Question 8 of 10",
        "Q":"Which SQL statement is used to return only different values?",
        "Options":["SELECT DIFFERENT","SELECT DISTINCT","SELECT UNIQUE ",""],
        "Answer":1
    },
    {
        "id": "9",
        "Question":"Question 9 of 10",
        "Q":"Which SQL keyword is used to sort the result-set?",
        "Options":["ORDER BY","ORDER ","SORT","SORT BY"],
        "Answer":3
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "Question":"Question 10 of 10",
        "Q":"What is the most common type of join?",
        "Options":["JOINED TABLE","JOIN","INNER JOIN",""],
        "Answer":2
    }

]}